（Ｌナンド）はぁ　はぁ　はぁ…。
（Ｓナンド）はぁ…。
（Ｍナンド）ああ～…。
Brother, I'm starving.
（Ｌナンド）にいちゃん　腹減ったよ～。
You'll have to hold on till we get to Balbadd.
（Ｓナンド）バルバッドまでの辛抱だ。→
It's a mess over there right now.
あそこは　今　荒れてるからな。
Even so, we're still going to need to get some money.
（Ｍナンド）だとしても
まずは　先立つものがないと。
Brother, look over there!
（Ｌナンド）にいちゃん　あれ　あれ。
（Ｓナンド）あっ？
（シンドバッド）ぐぅ～…。
≫ザッ　ザッ　ザッ（足音）
（Ｓナンド）うっ！
（Ｌナンド）酒臭っ！
He reeks of alcohol.
（Ｍナンド）酔い潰れてますね。
Must've passed out from all that alcohol.
んん～…　はははっ。
ぐぅ…。
akogare wo ima tsukanda
My desires are within reach.
♪♪～
daikansei no namari ni
If the loud, welcoming cheers
kokochiyoku utaretanara
shoot home straight into your heart,
saa tobikomou
then come and jump in!
ashita kara umare kawaru toka
People say they'll change the next day.
♪♪～
dareka ga mikiri tsuketa toka
But they give up so easily.
kono machi no style toka
That's just how it is here.
sonna mono ni nagasare tsuzukete
They get swept away by those excuses day by day.
kado no toreta genseki ni ha
They're nothing more than a chip, swept off the edge
kitto daremo you ha nai
and no longer needed by anyone.
♪♪～
fushigi to tobira no mukou ni ha
Guess what? Out there,
v.i.p nanoru yatsu ha naku
no one's swaggering around like a VIP.
daremo ga kunou no hate sa ore mo
Everyone suffers their own heartaches, myself included.
akogare wo ima tsukanda
But my desires are within reach.
♪♪～
mi wo yudanereba ii  kaji ha kono te ni
Throw yourself in with abandon. I've got the wheel.
mitsu kazoete the show time
On the count of three, it's show time!
daikansei no namari ni
If the loud, welcoming cheers
kokochiyoku utaretanara
shoot home straight into your heart,
saa tobikomou
then come and jump in!
♪♪～
7th Night
His Name is Sinbad
Hey Mor?
（アラジン）ねえねえ　モルさんは
故郷への船に乗るために→
You're going to Balbadd so you can catch a ship back to your homeland, right?
バルバッドに行くんだよね？
（モルジアナ）はい。
Yes.
And also because I wanted to see you two again.
それと
ずっと会いたいと思ってたんです→
あなたと　アリババさんに→
I wanted to give my thanks to both you and Alibaba.
お礼がしたくて。
お礼？
Your thanks?
I am so grateful to you both for giving me back my future.
私に
自由な未来を与えてくださって→
本当に　感謝しています。
ありがと　アラジン。
Thank you so much, Aladdin.
あっ…　やめてよ　モルさん。
No! Stop that, Mor!
I'm pretty sure I can speak for Alibaba too when I say that neither of us freed you just to get your thanks!
僕もだけど
アリババくんも　お礼なんか→
いらないって言うと思うよ。
Huh?
えっ？
だって　アリババくんは→
I'm sure he did it just because it was the right thing to do!
そういう優しい人だからね。
ふふっ。
あぁ～あ→
Now I really want to see him again too.
僕も　早く　アリババくんに
会いたくなっちゃったな～。
As long as we keep following this road, we will.
会えますよ　この道をたどれば。
♪♪～
うん　そうだね。
Yeah, that's true.
あっ。
Hello there!
（シンドバッド）やあ　君たち。
What a beautiful day we're having!
今日は　いい天気だね。
（２人）あっ！
モルさん　危ない！　下がって！
Mor, stand back! He's dangerous!
大丈夫です。
ここは　私に任せてください！
No, it's okay! I will handle this!
モンスターかもしれないよ！
（シンドバッド）あっ　いや…　違うんだ。
Wait, I think you're misunderstanding the situation!
He might be a monster!
Please hear me out.
I am aware. I will take care of him!
分かりました。　私が　やります！
（シンドバッド）話を聞いてくれ。
Thanks for lending me some clothes, Aladdin.
（シンドバッド）服を貸してくれて
ありがとう　アラジン。→
俺の名はシン。
バルバッドへ向かう途中で→
My name's Sin.
I was on my way to Balbadd when thieves robbed me clean.
泥棒に　身ぐるみ　やられてね。
I see. I'm sorry, mister.
そっか。　ごめんよ　おじさん。
I'm sorry for my reaction too.
どうも　僕は　砂漠越えのせいで→
Crossing the desert has made me a bit too wary of danger.
危険なものに
敏感になってるようだよ。
Oh? You've crossed the desert?
ほう～　砂漠を越えたのか？
I crossed the Central Desert, coming from the northern Tenzan Plateau.
北天山高原から
中央砂漠を越えてきたのさ。
I saw so many strange plants and animals!
珍しい植物や生き物が
たくさんいたよ。
That's great.
（シンドバッド）いいね～。
It feels great when you encounter new lands and new knowledge.
未知なる土地や知識に出会う→
あの高揚感。→
The confidence, experience, and bonds of friendship that are formed through adventuring are priceless.
道を切り開くことで
生まれる自信　経験。→
仲間たちとの命懸けの絆。
Adventures are splendid. They are truly what makes a man a man.
冒険はいい。
まさに　男のロマンだよ。
I understand! I totally understand how you feel, mister!
分かる！
分かるよ　おじさんの気持ち。
うん。　それに→
And meeting lovely ladies like you is also part of the adventure.
君のような　かわいらしい
お嬢さんとの出会いも→
旅の楽しみの一つだね。
はあ…。
Oh.
Wait.
すぅ～…　潮の香り。
I can smell the sea.
Once you get to the top of that hill, you should be able to see it.
その丘を越えれば
見えるはずだよ。
はぁ　はぁ　はぁ…。
♪♪～
This is...
ここが…。
バルバッド。
Balbadd!
Yeah.
（シンドバッド）
そう。　この港町を首都に→
This is the nation of Balbadd,
近海の大小数百の島々を束ねる→
made up of this port city as its capital and
hundreds of various islands in its adjacent waters.
一大海洋国家　バルバッド王国だ。
It's a great oceanic nation.
♪♪～
With relations to the oases in the north,
（シンドバッド）
この国は　北のオアシス都市群→
small nations in the northeast,
北東の小国群
西のパルテビアやレーム帝国…→
and Partevia and Laem Empires in the west,
Balbadd has flourished as the center of maritime trade since times untold.
海上交易の中心地として
古来より　栄えてたんだ。→
The royal family here is the Saluja and
they've governed this nation for generations.
代々
サルージャ家という王族が治めて→
もり立ててきたのだがね。
♪♪～
「王政打破」？
"Down with the monarchy"?
The country fell into disorder with the death of the previous king.
（シンドバッド）先王が亡くなってからは
国が乱れているようだ。→
But this place here is safe!
でも　ここなら安全だよ。→
俺が　いつも使う
国一番の高級ホテル。
It's the best hotel in the country and the one I always stay at.
I'll pay for your rooms. Stay as long as you'd like.
宿代は　俺が出そう。
好きなだけ
ここに泊まってゆくといい。
Wow, thanks mister! You're so rich!
うわ～　ありがとう　おじさん。
お金持ちなんだね。
はははっ。　ははははっ！
Who are you?
（ガード）なんだ!?　貴様！
（ガード）怪しいヤツめ！
Get out of here, you weirdo!
（シンドバッド）えっ？
俺のどこが怪しいっていうんだ？
What's so weird about me?
（ガード）どう見ても怪しいだろうが！
Everything!
Him and his mouth.
（マスルール）いましたね。
（ジャーファル）まったく…→
Honestly. What is he doing?
何をなさっているんだ　あの人は。
≪（シンドバッド）ちゃんと　はいてる。
はぁ…。
≪（ガード）服が小さいじゃないか！
Your clothes are way too revealing!
（ジャーファル）お待ちなさい。
（ガードたち）あっ…。
Please stop.
It seems as if our master has inconvenienced you.
（ジャーファル）私どもの主人が
ご迷惑をおかけしました。→
As he said, please let us cover your room fees.
主人の言葉どおり
宿代は　こちらに　お任せください。
Thank you, friends of Sin!
ありがとう
部下の　おにいさんたち！
（ジャーファル）さあ　あなたは　とっとと
そのみっともない格好を→
And you, please do something about your inappropriate attire.
なんとかしてください。
じゃあな　アラジンとモルジアナ。
See you later, Aladdin and Morgiana!
Let's eat together!
あとで　飯でも　一緒に食おう。
あっ。
（シンドバッド）驚いたろう？
お前と同じ　ファナリスとはな。
Were you surprised to see another Fanalis?
（マスルール）
はあ…。　まあ　珍しいっすからね。
Yes, I suppose so. We are a rare sight.
I'm sure the answer is no, but you didn't let everything get stolen, did you?
ところで　シン　まさか→
荷物を　すべて
盗られたわけではないですよね？
盗られたんだ。
Yes, I did.
えっ…。
ふっ。
Not just your clothes, but all of your
tools and everything you had on you?
服だけじゃなく
あらゆる道具まで？
すべて盗られた。
Yes, everything.
ああ～…。　あんたは
あれがなんだか　忘れたんですか!?
You... Have you forgotten what those tools are?
ははははっ。　大丈夫　大丈夫。→
Don't worry!
なんとかするから
俺に任せておけ。
I'll take care of it. Just leave it to me!
はぁ～。　まったく…→
Honestly...
いつになったら　王としての自覚が
生まれるんですか!?→
How long is it going to take you to start acting like a king?
You are Sinbad, the King of Sindria!
我がシンドリア国の主
シンドバッド王よ。
うわ～！　いい部屋だね～。
Wow, this is such a nice room!
ふふっ！　あははっ　ふふふふっ！
Wait, miss!
そうだ　おねえさん。
Where would we be able to find a ship headed to the Dark Continent?
暗黒大陸に行く船って
どこから乗れるのかな？
暗黒？　ああ～→
The Dark Continent?
Oh, you mean a ship traveling to the south.
南への船でございますね。→
That might be hard to find at the moment.
でしたら　今は難しいかと。
えっ？
実は…。
How come?
You see...
（アブマド）シ…　シンドバッドおじさん
お久しぶりでしな。
M-Mister Sinbad. It's been a while.
No need for pleasantries.
挨拶など不要だ。
俺の用件は　一つだけ→
I'm only here for one thing.
Reopen maritime trade with Sindria.
シンドリアとの船舶貿易を
再開しろ。→
俺と　お前らのおやじさんが
培ってきた→
Your father and I cultivated an alliance between our two nations. Are you trying to break that?
両国の関係を　ぶち壊す気か？
わ…　悪いけど
交易再開は　無理でし。→
I-I'm sorry, but it's impossible for me to reopen trade.
I already have my hands full with domestic issues here in Balbadd.
今　バルバッドは国内の大問題で→
手いっぱいなんでしよ。
ああ？
What?
The Fog Troupe?
霧の団？
はい。
Yes.
This city often gets fog, but recently, a group of thieves has been appearing with the fog.
この街は　よく霧が出るのですが→
最近　その霧に紛れて　盗賊団が→
現れるようになったのです。
Just a group of stinking thieves...
（アブマド）コソ泥のくせに
２年前に　城の宝物庫を破って→
But two years ago, they broke into the royal treasury and their numbers have been growing ever since.
どんどん膨れ上がって…　しかも→
They equip themselves with some strange magic.
不思議な魔術まで　身に付けて→
The army can't do anything against them.
They've become a powerful anarchist force.
もう国軍も手に負えない
一大反政府軍に→
なってしまったんでしよ。
（メイド）ただ　襲うのは主に→
But they only attack the mansions of nobles and national trading vessels,
貴族の館や　国の貿易船で→
and they redistribute the goods and money they
gain, so some people are considering them heroes.
そこで奪った金品を
分け与えてくれるので→
英雄視する人たちもいます。
Heroic thieves...
義賊というやつですか？
Heroic thieves? Yeah right.
何が義賊でし。
国庫を傷つければ→
By stealing from the treasury, all they've done is raise the taxes!
税金が増えるだけなのに。
国民は　バカでしね～。
The people are idiots.
You two have a terrible reputation.
（シンドバッド）お前ら　評判　悪いぞ。
うっ…。　しかたないんでし！
It's not our fault!
This really annoying guy just took over the Fog Troupe recently.
近頃　厄介なヤツが
霧の団のトップになるし。
Ever since, the riots and upheavals have gotten worse.
その人が現れて以来
ますます騒乱が→
激しくなっているんです。
新しいトップ…。
The new leader...
はい。　名前は　アリババ。
あっ。
Yes, his name is Alibaba.
They call him Miracle Man Alibaba.
（メイド）
怪傑アリババと呼ばれています。
Why on earth did he have to show up now of all times!
まったく…　なんだって　今頃→
あいつが出てくるんでし。
（サブマド）兄上　その話は…。
（アブマド）あっ…。
Ahbmad, shh!
（サブマド）しぃ～！
（アブマド）と…　とにかく→
A-At any rate, because of the Fog Troupe, trade is impossible.
霧の団のせいで　交易は無理でし。
再開してほしけりゃ→
If you want to reopen trade that badly, you'll have to find your own solution.
おじさんが
自分で　なんとかするでしなぁ。
ほう～　なんとかしていいんだな？
You don't mind if I do?
（２人）うっ…。
（シンドバッド）
俺が　その霧の団とやらを→
I'll get rid of that Fog Troupe.
退治してやるよ。　軍隊も使わず→
I don't need your army either. We'll do it alone.
俺たちだけでな。
（２人）あぁ…。
怪傑アリババ。
きっと　別の人だよ。
Miracle Man Alibaba.
I'm sure that's not our Alibaba.
Yeah...
そう…　ですね。
よっと。
≫ガチャ（窓の音）
I can't wait to see Alibaba again.
あぁ～あ　早く会いたいな
アリババくんに。
Are you all right, Ahbmad?
（サブマド）大丈夫かな？　兄上。
（アブマド）いいでし。→
Just fine.
No matter what he does, reopening trade with Sindria is impossible.
シンドリアとの交易再開は
どのみち　不可能だけど→
If he gets rid of the Fog Troupe in the process, well, all the better for us.
霧の団を倒してくれるなら
もうけものでし。
Kou Empire
Eat to your heart's content!
（シンドバッド）遠慮なく　やりたまえ。
バルバッド名物→
Balbadd's speciality, herb cooked Eumera sea bream.
エウメラ鯛の香草焼きだ。
わあ～！
はうっ！
ふふっ。→
I haven't introduced you to my men yet, have I?
そういえば
部下の紹介が　まだだな。→
These are Jafar and Masrur.
ジャーファルとマスルールだ。
Morgiana, Masrur is a Fanalis.
モルジアナ　このマスルールはな
ファナリスなんだよ。
What?
えっ。
（シンドバッド）君もだろ？→
You are too, aren't you?
You two have the same eyes.
目元が　そっくりだな　二人とも。
♪♪～
Nice to meet you.
どうも。
あっ…。
You too.
どうも。
♪♪～
So what do you plan on doing?
（ジャーファル）で　どうするのです？→
You made such a bold statement to those
brothers but you don't have any of your tools.
道具もないのに
あんな安請け合いをして。
Hi! I'm Aladdin!
Nice to meet you.
It'll work out.
You and Mor are from the same place, right?
（シンドバッド）なんとかなるさ。
（ジャーファル）おい。
What?
At Sindria's founding, the previous king of Balbadd taught me a lot about trading.
シンドリアを建国したとき…。
すごくおっきいね。
Yes.
You're so big! Are other Fanalis like him?
バルバッド先王には
貿易について　教わったんだ。→
I'm not sure...
あの人は　亡くなってしまったが→
But Ugo's still in a league of his own.
Even though he's no longer with us, I owe him a great debt.
大きな借りがある。
この国を　みすみす→
Let me introduce you to my friend, Ugo!
I can't stand by and watch his nation fall to chaos.
戦火に沈めさせはしないさ。
プーーッ（笛の音）
（ジャーファル）ぶぅ～！
うっ！　ん？
うわぁ～！→
アラジン…　君も　マギなのか？
Aladdin, you're also a Magi?
「も」？　おじさん
ほかにも　マギを知ってるのかい？
Also? Mister, do you know other Magi?
Yup.
（シンドバッド）ああ。
おじさんって　一体　何者なの？
Mister, who are you?
俺は　シンドバッドだ。
The name is Sinbad.
あっ…。
ふふっ。
えっ？
あれ？→
What?
Ha-Haven't you heard of me?
し…　知らないの？
シンドバッドの冒険とか…　ほら。
The adventures of Sinbad! I'm him!
Who?
ん？
んん！　幾重にも旅と航海を重ね→
The man who has traveled countless roads and sailed untold voyages,
who has navigated the world's seven seas,
世界の７つの海を冒険し→
who has conquered seven dungeons and built his own country!
７つの迷宮を攻略して
自らの国を打ち立てた男。→
The master of seven djinn, high king of the seven seas,
７人のジンの主　七海の覇王→
それが　シンドバッド。
Sinbad!
す…　すごい…　んだよね？
Th-That's... amazing?
あっ　あぁ…。
僕には　よく分からないけど。
I'm not sure if I really understand though...
分からないの？　マギなのに？
You don't?
Even though you're a Magi?
Mister, what exactly is a Magi?
ねえ　おじさん　マギって何かな？
僕は　まだ
自分のことも分からないんだよ。
I'm not even sure I understand myself.
うん…　一つ言えることは→
What I can say is that this here is something only a Magi could do.
これが　マギということだよ。→
Only a Magi can produce enough magoi to so easily
summon a djinn for such an extended period of time.
ジンを　やすやすと
実体化させ続けるほどの→
魔力の出力。　魔力とは→
Magoi refers to the energy produced by rukh.
ルフが生み出す　エネルギーだ。→
Ordinary people are able to use only the rukh available inside of their bodies,
普通の人間は
自分の中のルフしか使えないが→
but Magi are not limited and can use the rukh energy all around them limitlessly.
マギは　自分以外のルフが生む
エネルギーをも→
無限に使うことができるんだ。
♪♪～
You Magi are loved by the rukh.
君は　ルフたちに愛されている。→
Magi are really amazing.
いや～
マギってのは　ほんとにすごいね。
Actually, I have a request for someone as amazing as you are.
そうだ。　そんな　すごい君に→
一つ頼みがあるんだが。
なんだい？
What is it?
この国を
騒がせている盗賊を捕まえる→
Would you be willing to help me capture the group of thieves that's causing trouble here?
手助けをしてくれないか？
Wait!
ちょっと！
待ってください　シン。→
Hold on, Sin.
Do you plan on getting these children involved?
こんな子供たちを
巻き込む気ですか？
Why not?
（シンドバッド）なぜ　いけない？
アラジンは　マギなのだ。→
Aladdin is a Magi.
He is one touched by destiny and has the appropriate skills for his position.
運命に選ばれるだけの
能力がある。→
And also, we don't have a single metal vessel on us right now.
それに　俺たちには　今　金属器が→
一つもないしな。
（ジャーファル）誰のせいですか！
And whose fault is that?
モルさん　どうしよう？
What should we do, Mor?
私は　暗黒大陸に渡りたいのです。
I wish to travel to the Dark Continent.
霧の団を倒せば　船が
出るようになるのでしょうか？
If we defeat the Fog Troupe, the
ships will be able to sail again, right?
（シンドバッド）
そのために　俺たちは来た。
That's why we're here.
We're also here to look for someone.
それから
私たちは　人捜しをしています。
If we can successfully deal with this situation, could you ask this nation's king for help in our search?
無事に解決したら
この国の王様に　力を貸すよう→
頼んでいただけますか？
（シンドバッド）請け負おう。
Granted. I shall.
どうでしょう？　アラジン。
What do you think, Aladdin?
We'll do it!
うん。　やるよ　盗賊退治。
Great! Then let's start planning, Aladdin!
そうか。　では　アラジン→
早速　作戦を練ろう。
うん。
Okay!
Morgiana, you can wait at the hotel.
（シンドバッド）そして　モルジアナ
君は　宿で　待っていてくれたまえ。
えっ？
（シンドバッド）いくらファナリスでも→
What?
Even if you are a Fanalis, I couldn't let a lady like you fight.
女の子を　戦わせらんないよ。→
Come now.
さあ…。
ドスン！
私も　戦います。
I will fight too.
Yes'm.
はい…。
（ジャーファル）霧の団が狙うのは
豪商アルジャリス→
We believe the Fog Troupe's aim is
either the wealthy merchant, Aljaris',
もしくは　貴族のハルドゥーブ→
どちらかの屋敷だと思われます。
or the noble, Haldhub's, mansion.
Why do you say that?
（シンドバッド）なぜ言い切れる？
（ジャーファル）こちらから→
False information has been spread
about the movements of the army.
国軍の動きに関する偽情報を
流しました。→
The Fog Troupe appears to have
supporters even within the government.
霧の団には　政府内部にも
シンパがいるようなので。
Even within the government...
政府内にもか。
うん。
Yes.
The Fog Troupe is more popular
among the people than we imagined.
想像以上に　霧の団は→
義賊として
人気が　高まっているようです。
ふむ…。
あの…。
Hm.
Excuse me.
If the people support the Fog Troupe, are we
really doing the right thing by capturing them?
国民が支持しているなら→
霧の団を捕まえるのは
正しいことなのでしょうか？
I think so.
（シンドバッド）俺は正しいと思ってる。→
They distribute the money they steal to the
people, thereby gaining the people's support.
彼らは
奪った金を　市民にばらまき→
支持を得ている。
That's why the people call them chivalrous thieves.
故に　義賊と呼ばれるわけだ。→
But I think the thieves may only do that to make their crimes seem justifiable.
だが　俺は考える。→
それは　犯罪を
自己正当化するための行為→
Or perhaps we are hearing a lot of propaganda.
あるいは　ただの
プロパガンダでは…　とかね。→
Well, that's what I've come up with.
まっ
そんな具合に　俺は自分で…→
That's my story and I'm sticking to it.
自分の頭で考え
正しいと思える答えを出した。→
You guys should also spend some time thinking this over,
君たちも　何がいいのか
精いっぱい　自分で考え→
and act according to your conclusions.
そうして導き出した答えを信じて
行動してほしい。
That's how I've managed to get this far.
俺は　そうやって
道を切り開いてきたが→
What do you guys think?
君たちは　どうだろうか？
♪♪～
（ジャーファル）霧が出てきましたね。→
The fog has rolled in.
二人とも
来てくれて　うれしいですよ。
I'm glad the two of you decided to join us.
I'm still not sure what the right thing to do is though.
僕には　まだ　何が正しいか
よく分からないんだよ。
But I came all this way to see my friend.
でも　僕は
大切な友達に会いたくて→
ここまで来たんだ。
会えるなら　なんでもするよ。
I'll do whatever it takes to see him again.
I'll capture these thieves.
盗賊だって　捕まえてみせるさ。
うん。　いい答えです。
Good answer.
Are Sinbad and Masrur the only
ones guarding the other mansion?
あの…　あちらの守りは→
シンドバッドさんたち
だけなのですか？
ご心配なく。　腐っても→
Do not worry.
Sinbad might seem a little shady, but his title as the high king of the seven seas isn't just for show.
七海の覇王の二つ名は
だてじゃありませんから。
はっ　はっ…　はっくしゅん！
うぅ…　夜は冷えるな。
（マスルール）そうっすね。
It's so cold at night.
It is.
（シンドバッド）バカ！　動くなよ。
Stop! Don't move!
（マスルール）
風よけにしないでくださいよ。
Don't use me as a wind breaker.
≪ガチャ
≪（ハルドゥーブ）こら！　そこの二人！→
You two down there!
Stop chattering and take guarding my mansion seriously!
くっちゃべってないで
しっかり警備しろ！
I can't believe the army's so shorthanded that
they could only spare the two of you to guard me.
国軍の手が足りずに
たった二人の警備など→
不安で　飯も食えぬわ！
I'm so nervous I can't eat!
食ってますね。
いいご身分だな。
He's eating right now.
Must be rich.
あっ…。　ん？
はぁ　はぁ　はぁ…。
（シンドバッド）おい　あんた　大丈夫か？
Are you all right?
あっ！
なんだ!?
What was that?
♪♪～
I can't produce any milk.
お乳が…　出ないのよ。→
I need food.
If you get in our way, we'll ki-kill you!
どうしても　食べ物が必要なの…。
邪魔するなら…　こ…　殺すわ！
げっ！　スラムの犬どもか。
Ugh, those dogs from the slums are here.
しっ！　しっ！
これをやるから　どっか行け！
Here, fetch! Get out of here!
あっ！
♪♪～
そんなことをする必要はない。
There is no need for you to do this.
貴族の富は
元は　お前たちの税金だ。
The nobles' wealth comes from your taxes.
あぁ…。
払うに値しないと思うなら→
If you don't feel that they deserve it, then you should take it back.
遠慮なく　返してもらうがいい。
（シンドバッド）だが　命は取るなよ。
But do not take lives.
♪♪～
Right.
（マスルール）いいんすか？
（シンドバッド）はぁ…。→
Are you sure about this?
俺たちが約束したのは　霧の団を→
We only agreed to capture the Fog Troupe.
捕らえることだけだからな。
（シンドバッド）
この国は　もうダメかもな。
This country might already be too far gone though.
What's so funny?
It's just... so funny!
Mister Jafar, we think Mister Sinbad may have been attacked!
It sounds like people are having fun.
Aladdin, don't breathe in any of the mist!
Stay away!
It's the thieves! There's a huge group of them!
What's going on?
They seem to be caught in an illusion.
Did you notice the red mist?
That's not a product of human hands.
It must be strange magic.
Your Sword of Phantasmal Scarlet Fog is as frightening as ever, Zaynab.
Stop talking and start using your Sword of Corroding Golden Fog, Hassan.
Yeah, yeah.
Let's go!
Our target is that fat pig's mansion!
Go wild!
Let go!
Are you part of the army?
No. But for various reasons, I must apprehend you.
Bastard!
Another magical weapon!
That's right. It's the Sword of Shackling Ebon Fog.
Now you can't move a finger.
Kassim!
Let my comrades go.
Our leader and our main force have arrived.
はははっ。
何…　笑ってんだよ。
Kassim, heading your way!
ははははっ！
だってよ～　なんか…。
ジャーファルさん
シンドバッドさんたちの方が→
襲われたと…。
≫（兵士たち）ははははっ！→
≫ははっ！　ははははっ！
ん？
A girl?
なんか楽しそうだね。
あっ！
Mor!
アラジン
この霧を　吸ってはダメです！
うわっ！
≪（兵士）うわっ！
≪（兵士）く…　来るな！→
盗賊だ！　大軍だ！
何が起こっているの？
Now's your chance!
Grab the goods and run for it!
（ジャーファル）彼らは…
幻覚に惑わされているようですね。
I am searching for Alibaba.
気付きましたか？　この赤い霧。
In order to find him, I'll-
Ugo!
人間の技ではない。→
例の不思議な力なのでしょう。
♪♪～
I won't let you pass!
（ハッサン）相変わらず
おっかねぇなぁ　ザイナブ。→
I-It's no good!
There's no way we can beat that thing!
お前の赤幻霧刀は。
（ザイナブ）しゃべってる暇があるなら→
さっさと
あんたの黄蝕霧刀を使いな→
What's the matter, friend?
ハッサン。
（ハッサン）ふっ。　へい　へい。
Leave this one to me.
♪♪～
Wait...
さあ　行くぞ！
肥え太った豚野郎の屋敷だ！
遠慮は　いらねぇ～！
（一同）おお～！
うおっ！
うわっ…。
ぐっ！
放せ！
（団員）国軍か!?
いいえ。
ですが　訳あって　あなたたちを
捕らえさせていただきます。
Ali... baba?
てめぇ！
（ザイナブ）あっ！
♪♪～
nozoite miyou
Take a look
yubi bouenkyou
through your finger telescope.
これも…　魔法武器か…。
≪（カシム）そうさ　黒縛霧刀だ。
me ni mieru sekai ha subete kako no monogatari sa
The world you see before your eyes is a story already told.
♪♪～
（カシム）
お前は　もう　一歩も動けねぇよ。
kagayaku mirai wo miushinau na yo
Don't lose sight of the bright future ahead.
（ザイナブ）カシム！
（カシム）仲間を返してもらおうか。
kimi ni ha motto ippai yume to kibou ga arun da
You're destined to realize great hopes and dreams.
（ハッサン）お頭の本隊が来たぞ！
♪♪～
bootto shitetara minogashichau zo
But if you blink for too long, they'll leave you behind.
（団員）カシム　やべぇのが行った！
（カシム）ふん！
dekinai riyuu sagasu yori
Instead of searching for an excuse,
♪♪～
くっ…。
（カシム）女のガキ？
yatte mireba ii
why not just give it a try?
モルさん！
（覆面）あっ…。　はっ！
nozoite miyou
Take a look
うぅ…　ぐっ！
おい…。
ああっ？　くっ！
yubi bouenkyou
through your finger telescope.
♪♪～
yubi to yubi wo marume ryoume ni ate
Make circles with your fingers and put them around your eyes.
（カシム）
今のうちだ。　奪って　ずらかれ！
（団員たち）おお～！
imeeji shite sagashiteru mono
Picture your hopes and dreams!
（心の声）
≪僕は　アリババくんを捜すんだ≫
atama no naka no adobenchaaa
Picture your personal adventure story!
≪そのためなら…≫
ウーゴくん！
プーーッ！
（２人）ん？　ああ～！
doko he mukau?
Where are you headed?
（一同）うわ～！
yubi bouenkyou
What can you see
♪♪～
yubi no sono sukima ni nani ga mieru?
in the space between your fingers?
ここは　通らせないよ！
ダ…　ダメだ。　あんなの相手じゃ…。
（カシム）ちっ！
tooi you demo hontou ha chikai
It might seem far, but it's really not.
♪♪～
yogen no you na takaramono
It's a promise as valuable as any treasure!
どうした？　相棒。
（覆面）任せてくれ。
♪♪～
Do you plan on starting a war?
Tell me why you're with the Fog Troupe!
ドクン（鼓動）
あれ？
Next time: A Broken Promise.
8th Night
A Broken Promise
ドクン　ドクン　ドクン　ドクン
Leave me alone!
This is my problem!
あぁ…。
アリババ…　くん？
♪♪～
（カシム）
ひとつ　戦争でも　おっぱじめるか。
教えてよ　君が　霧の団にいる訳を。
（アリババ）ほっといてくれよ。
これは　俺の問題なんだ。
まずは、総選挙に向けた動き。
日本維新の会と太陽の党が昨日
正式に合流を決めたことについて
野田総理大臣がそれぞれ色を出し
ていたのに
混ざってグレーになったなどと批
判するなど